Translated by sviiseven / nReus & EnzoAquila
By the rain-soaked windowsill
I hum a nostalgic tune
In the emptiness of my young self's heart
A newborn warmth blossoms within
Hand in hand, returning home from the seaside dyed red of the sunset
What was nothing more than the usual carefree times,
Had now become very dear moments
On the corners of that old photo album, remain traces of teardrops
To the one who found them,
I convey to you, "Thank you, and farewell."
As I write this letter,
I dream of the good old days
Sleeping at the ocean's floor, remaining unnamed
A single bud, that will sprout into a pure heart
Hand in hand, we sleep together in the night
Underneath the shining starry sky
That warmth you provided for me,
The feeling lingers in my hands
In these distant, fading memories,
A gentle voice resonates
Telling me to pass on to you,
"Thank you, and farewell."
Hand in hand, returning home from the seaside dyed red of the sunset
What was nothing more than an ordinary moment,
Now had become a very dear moment
On the corners of that old photo album, remains traces of teardrops
To the one who found this,
Thank you, my favorite person
Those dear moments, they'll never come back